Look, he gets a variety of gender here.
The Miami Special Utility Authority for today's date.
Item number two is in the Cation, Ronnie.
Would you say the bus in the fourth place?
Thank you.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, let's pray.
Heavenly Father, would you just give thanks for another best of day on earth.
We thank you for this rain that we're receiving.
And we just thank you for the day.
We ask that you guide and direct our Council members,
giving them wisdom or to move this city forward as in your will.
And we just thank you so much for the M and their sacrifices
and been away from their families.
Lord, there's just, you know, it's incredible.
We just want to thank them.
For gifts of all our sins, thank you for sending Jesus.
His name we pray, amen.
Amen.
Please join me in the part.
Modulations to the five of the United States of America.
And to the ultimate for which it stands.
One nation under God.
Either this fool, or whatever he does.
I don't know.
The more is public input on schedule personal parenthesis.
I want the audience.
It was just to address the authority on the need of the agenda items.
Being none, item five is consent agenda staff is recommending item six through eight.
If there are no questions or objections out of the entertainer motion.
Motion to approve.
And a second.
Second.
Roll call.
Johnson.
Aye.
Weston.
Forster.
Aye.
I don't know.
As a proof of corporate associates engaged in the letter for accounting services for fiscal year 2016.
In 2017.
Dean any comments on that?
This is the standard approval that is going through.
They have them do our accounting services for the next system.
Any questions?
I think we've been very happy with their services.
Okay.
We have a motion to approve.
Motion.
And a second.
Second.
Roll call.
Forster.
Aye.
Western.
Johnson.
Aye.
Any new business date?
Any staff report during your packet?
Any announcements?
No.
Item 13 is adjourned.
We have a motion to adjourn.
Second.
Roll call.
Forster.
Aye.
Western.
Johnson.
Aye.
We're on apology.